[{"question":"What is the #1 beer in the world?","answer":"Budweiser claims the top spot as the world's most valuable beer brand for the first time, overtaking long-standing leader Bud Light. Budweiser's FIFA World Cup campaign last year was the brand's most expensive to date, reaching 3.2 billion football fans globally.","url":"https://www.beveragedaily.com/Article/2019/06/27/The-King-of-Beers-Budweiser-ranked-the-most-valuable-beer-brand-in-the-world","title":"The King of Beers: Budweiser ranked the most valuable beer brand ...","date":"27. 6. 2019"},{"question":"What are the top 10 beers in the world?","answer":"Here are the top 10 best-selling beers in the world for 2017.Coors Light.Corona.Harbin.Heineken.Bud Light.Tsingtao.Budweiser.","url":"https://vinepair.com/articles/10-biggest-beer-brands-world-2018/","title":"The 10 Best Selling Beers In The World - 2018 | VinePair","date":"13. 11. 2018"},{"question":"What is the best beer in the world 2020?","answer":"So, fill your favorite beer glass with our picks of the best beers to drink.Best Overall: Schneider Aventinus Weizen-Eisbock. ... Best Light: Estrella Inedit Damm. ... Best Low Carb: Lagunitas DayTime IPA. ... Best German: Weihenstaphaner Hefe Weissbier. ... Best IPA: Dogfish Head 90-Minute. ... Best Sour: The Lost Abbey Red Poppy Ale.Další položky...•","url":"https://www.liquor.com/best-beers-4846348","title":"The 13 Best Beers to Drink in 2020 - Liquor.com","date":"22. 7. 2020"},{"question":"Who drinks the most beer?","answer":"The country that imbibes the most brews has its own, controversial version of Budweiser beer.CountryBeer Consumption RankLiters Consumed Per CapitaCzech Republic1142.4 (37.6 gallons)Seychelles2114.6 (30.3 gallons)Germany3 (tie)104.7 (27.7 gallons)Austria3 (tie)104.7 (27.7 gallons)6 dalších řádků•30. 9. 2017","url":"https://www.usnews.com/news/best-countries/articles/2017-09-30/these-10-countries-drink-the-most-beer","title":"These 10 Countries Drink the Most Beer | Best Countries | US News","date":""},{"question":"What are the top 5 beers in the world?","answer":"These are the most popular beers in the worldCoors - 26.5 million.Corona - 28.8 million.Yanjing - 29.7 million.Harbin - 29.9 million.Heineken - 34.3 million.Skol - 35.1 million.Bud Light - 44.8 million.Tsingtao - 49.0 million.Další položky...•","url":"https://www.kgun9.com/news/these-are-the-most-popular-beers-in-the-world","title":"These are the most popular beers in the world - Kgun","date":"13. 9. 2018"},{"question":"What's the worst beer to drink?","answer":"The 10 Absolute Worst Tasting Beers, RankedMichelob Ultra. PIN IT.Bud Light Chelada. PIN IT. Alison Cassidy. ... Corona Light. PIN IT. Melissa Miller. ... Bud Light. PIN IT. Erin Haydon. ... Busch Light. PIN IT. Michelle Miller. ... Keystone Light. PIN IT. Sofia Gonzalez.Natural Ice. PIN IT. Alex Frank. ... Coors Light. PIN IT. Sharon Cho. ... Další položky...","url":"https://spoonuniversity.com/lifestyle/worst-tasting-beers","title":"The 10 Worst Tasting Beers Ever, Ranked - Spoon University","date":""},{"question":"What is the world's best tasting beer?","answer":"These are 10 of the best tasting beers—sample a few and try claiming that beer is still the worst.Leinenkugel's Summer Shandy. ... Bud Light Lime. ... Shock Top. ... Landshark IPA. ... Blue Moon. ... Abita Strawberry Lager. ... Miller High Life. ... Samuel Adams Whitewater IPA.Další položky...","url":"https://spoonuniversity.com/lifestyle/best-tasting-beers-10","title":"The 10 Best Tasting Beers for People Who Hate the Taste of Beer","date":""},{"question":"What is the best selling beer?","answer":"Bud Light1. Bud Light. Bud Light, first sold nationwide in 1982, is by far America's favorite beer. Its parent company, Anheuser-Busch InBev, shipped more than 33 million barrels of the light lager in 2017 — double the shipments of the next most popular beer.","url":"https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/food/2018/10/17/beer-consumption-these-americas-26-top-selling-beers/38104743/","title":"Beer consumption: These are America's 26 top-selling beers","date":"17. 10. 2018"},{"question":"What cheap beer has the most alcohol?","answer":"Get Drunk Not BrokeBrandABV Alcohol % by VolumePrice Per 1oz. Pure AlcoholKeystone Light4.13%$1.14Colt 45 Malt Liquor6.1%$1.15Miller High Life4.6%$1.17Schlitz Beer4.7%$1.1888 dalších řádků•14. 4. 2013","url":"http://getdrunknotfat.com/get-drunk-not-broke/","title":"Get Drunk Not Broke | Cheapest Booze for Your Buck","date":""},{"question":"What was the best selling beer of 2019?","answer":"Stella Artois1) Stella Artois Taking the top spot as the number one selling beer is this 600-year-old Belgian lager.","url":"https://wisk.ai/top-selling-beers-2019-sales-data/","title":"Top Selling Beers Of 2019 So Far (Based On Sales Data) | WISK","date":"23. 10. 2019"},{"question":"What is the cheapest beer?","answer":"The 10 Cheapest Beers Every Student Should Know AboutNatty Light. You always remember your first love, and trust me — the more you're you drink it, the better it gets. ... Narragansett Lager. It has one of the highest ratings for lagers on beeradvocates.com. ... Keystone Light. ... Bud Light. ... Rainier. ... Busch. ... Budweiser.","url":"https://spoonuniversity.com/lifestyle/cheapest-beers-everyone-should-know-about","title":"The 10 Cheapest Beers Everyone (Especially Students) Should ...","date":""},{"question":"What is Australia's number 1 beer?","answer":"Victoria Bitter Known as the strongest beer in Australia, VB stays true to its name with its bitterness and full-bodied flavour.","url":"https://www.bhg.com.au/15-best-beers-in-australia","title":"15 Best Beers in Australia | Better Homes and Gardens","date":"18. 10. 2019"},{"question":"Which country drinks the most alcohol?","answer":"France consumed the most alcohol than any other top country by GDP and also has an above-average life expectancy.","url":"https://www.alcohol.org/guides/global-drinking-demographics/","title":"Global Drinking Demographics | Alcohol.org","date":""},{"question":"What is a popular beer?","answer":"The most popular beers in America48% Guinness. Brand. The most popular and the 12th most famous beer.48% Corona. Brand. ... 46% Samuel Adams. Brand. ... 46% Heineken. Brand. ... 42% Budweiser. Brand. ... Explore your very own audience with YouGov's new Audience Explorer. Try the FREE Audience Explorer.41% Blue Moon. Brand. ... 40% Bud Light. Brand.Další položky...","url":"https://today.yougov.com/ratings/food/popularity/beers/all","title":"The most popular beers in America | Food | YouGov Ratings","date":""},{"question":"What is a good beer?","answer":"The 21 Best Beers You Can Buy at Your Local StoreFirestone Walker Pivo Hoppy Pils. drizly.com. ... Great Lakes Dortmunder Gold Lager. Great Lakes Brewing Co. ... Oskar Blues Dale's Pale Ale. drizly.com. ... Sierra Nevada Pale Ale. ... Bell's Two Hearted Ale IPA. ... Sierra Nevada Hazy Little Thing IPA. ... Lagunitas DayTime IPA. ... Orval Trappist Ale.Další položky...•","url":"https://www.townandcountrymag.com/leisure/drinks/g32099906/best-beers/","title":"21 Best Beers to Drink 2020 - Top Rated Beers to Try","date":"9. 5. 2020"}]
